invoiceable.co 2015-04-07

# Invoiceable - free invoicing - Privacy Policy

## What we collect

We may collect the following information from you:

  * Your full name and email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Login and use of the Invoiceable system
  * Internal record keeping
  * User support

We may use the information to improve our products and services.

We may periodically directly send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. You agree to receive these emails as part of our standard Terms of Service.

We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Payment and financial details

All payments to Invoiceable are billed through a PCI compliant third party payment processor (PayPal). No financial details are stored on our servers. All financial data collected on our website is immediately posted through a 256-bit SSL encrypted connection to the third party payment processor.

## How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

Any data saved inside these cookies is encrypted and made as secure as possible. We mainly use cookies to store session information and to remember certain preferences that you set.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Your personal information

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your email address to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Invoiceable Ltd, Suite 147, 155 Minories, London, EC3N 1AD.

If you believe that any information we are holding about/on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. Terminating your account

If you wish to terminate your account you can do so via the My Account settings page. Once we receive the termination request, we will terminate your account and any data relating to that account, such as projects and invoices. Please note that there is no undo to this procedure.

## Changes

Invoiceable may change this policy, without notice, from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

This policy is effective from 31st August 2012.
